* * * Subtitles by dylux * * *
( Growling Softly )
( Slurping )
( Typing ) ( Hisses )
( Ripley Narrating ) My mommy always said there were no monsters .
No real ones .
But there are . ( Chattering )
( Man ) We 've seen no additional defects .
She 's perfect . Mm-hmm .
( Breathing Heavily )
( Electronic Whirring )
( Machine Beeping )
Careful .
Two centimeters .
Okay .
Yeah .
Ready with that amnio .
( Beeping Continues )
Oh . And ...
there it is .
- ( Gasps ) - ( Exhales )
No .
( Alarm Beeping )
( Clicks ) Be careful .
( Alarm Stops )
( Screeches )
Jesus .
Clamp .
What about her ? Can we keep her alive ?
How 's the host ?
- ( Beeping ) - Doing well .
Sew her back up .
( Mouths Word )
Excellent work , everybody .
( Screaming )
( Alien Screeching , Faint )
( Hatch Opens )
And how is our Number 8 today ?
Appears to be in good health .
Hmm ? How good ? Excellent ,
as in completely off our projected charts .
Look at the scar tissue .
See the recession ? This is from three days ago ?
Exactly . Oh , this is good .
This is very good .
You 're gonna make us all very proud .
( Grunting )
( Gasps , Wheezing )
( Choking )
( Groans )
No . ( Panting )
Don 't . I 'm all right .
Now try this .
( Mouthing Word )
- Hand . - Close .
Glove .
( Woman Over Monitor ) Number 8 ?
Fruit .
( Woman Continues ) Good . Cherries . It 's unprecedented .
Totally . She 's operating ...
at a completely adult capacity .
What about her memories ? There are gaps .
- And some degree ofsynaptic dissonance . - ( Woman ) You know this .
She 's freaked . ( Woman ) Come on .
It has connective difficulties ,
caused by a biochemical imbalance , causing emotional autism .
Certain reactions-All right , wait a second !
It has memories . Why does it have memories ?
Well , I 'm guessing , but ... inherited memories ,
passed down generationally at a genetic level ...
by the aliens , like its strength .
Plus a , uh , highly evolved form of instinct .
An unexpected benefit from the genetic crossing .
Oh , ho , ho , ho , ho . I see .
Stupid me . Ofcourse .
An unexpected benefit of the genetic process .
Oh ! And I didn 't even think of that !
Let 's try this one .
Ripley ?
Ripley .
Ripley , what is it ?
Ripley ? Ripley ?
( Man ) You 're not thinking termination ?
Oh , boy , am I thinking termination .
General , we do not perceive this to be a problem .
Ellen Ripley died trying to wipe this species out .
For all intents and purposes , she succeeded .
I 'm not anxious to see her taking up her old hobbies .
That won 't happen . We won 't tell her .
Oh , I see . And that 's supposed to comfort me ?
( Beeping ) ( Male Electronic Voice ) Identification , please .
( Exhaling )
( Whirring , Buzzes )
Please try again . ( Exhaling )
Thank you , General Perez .
Bottom line is , she looks at me funny one time ,
I 'm putting her down .
Okay , as far as I 'm concerned , Number 8 ...
is a meat ... by-product .
Her Majesty here is the real payoff .
When does she start producing ? Days .
Less maybe .
We need the cargo . I told you , it 's on its way .
( No Audible Dialogue )
( Roaring )
( Growling )
Fork .
- Fuck . - It 's - It 's " fork . "
How did you - -
How did ... we get you ?
Yes . ( Fork Clinks )
( Sighs )
Hard work . We used blood samples ...
from Fiori Sixteen on ice ,
where you died .
We 've remade you . We cloned you .
Fiori Sixteen .
Does that ring a bell ?
Are you remembering something ?
- Does it grow ? - Yeah .
Very rapidly .
( Chuckles ) It 's a queen .
How did you know that ?
She 'll breed . You 'll die .
Everyone in the company will die .
In the-In the-In the company ?
Weyland-Yutani . Ripley 8 's former employers .
Terran growth conglomerate . They had ...
defense contracts under the military .
Oh , they went under decades ago , Gediman . Way before your time .
Bought out by Wal-Mart .
Fortunes ofwar . ( Chuckles )
( Fork Clinks ) I think you will find that , uh ,
things have changed a great deal since your time .
I doubt that .
We 're not flying blind here , you know .
It 's United Systems Military , not some greedy corporation .
Oh . ( Chuckles )
Well , it won 't make any difference .
You 're still gonna die .
How do you feel about that ?
I wish you could understand what we 're trying to do here .
The potential for this species goes way beyond urban pacification .
New alloys , new vaccines .
Nothing like this we 've ever seen on any world before .
You should be very proud .
Oh .
I am .
And the animal itself -
wondrous .
The potential , unbelievable , once we 've tamed them .
( Chuckles )
Roll over . Play dead .
Heel ? Mm-hmm .
You can 't teach it tricks .
Why not ? We 're teaching you .
Hey , son , I 'll give you my authorization code .
It 's E-A-T-M-E . ( Beeps )
( Man Over Speaker ) I 'm sorry , sir . Could you repeat that ?
Little prick .
You know ,
no matter how many times you see it ,
the sight of a woman all strapped up in a chair like that just -
( Sighs ) ( Chuckles ) What ?
Just bring us in on a 3-0 descent , would ya ?
And ride the parallel . Darlin ' , it is done .
Good girl .
You , uh , want anything there , trigger ?
Hmm . Yeah . How ' bout a cup ofcoffee ?
Anything else , while your mouth 's warm , I mean ?
( Computer Beeps ) Little milk .
Hey , don 't cut thrust till about 600 meters ,
and we 'll give ' em a little scare .
Vriess . Call .
Lock down . We 're gonna dock .
( Whirring )
♪ ( Whistling " Popeye The Sailor Man " ) ♪
( Whirring Stops ) ( Thuds )
♪ ( Whistling Continues ) ♪
( Whirring )
- Hey , Call ? - Yep ?
What has two thumbs , one eye ,
a pink tongue ...
and screws like a god ?
What ?
Two thumbs , one eye , a pink tongue ...
and screws like a god ?
( Sighs ) What ?
( Gasps )
( Man ) Time to enjoy some of the general 's hospitality , Christie .
Great . Army food .
Yeah . It 'll do till we get the family wagon up to spec , I reckon .
Yeah . That is if the natives are friendly .
How 's that ?
Good .
We expecting any , uh , trouble ?
Nah . From Perez , I doubt it . But you never know . We 've been there before .
♪ ♪ ( Whistling " Popeye The Sailor Man " )
( Making Monkey Sounds )
( Screeches )
( Monkey Sounds Continue ) ( Clicks Tongue )
( Grunts )
What is wrong with you ?
( Man ) Just a little target practice .
Vriess isn 't complaining .
Goddamn it !
Johner , you son of a bitch !
Come on , man . You didn 't feel a thing .
( Clangs )
You are an inbred motherfucker , you know that ?
( Making Monkey Sounds )
I 'll take the knife back now .
Whoa .
( Vriess ) Call , forget it .
He 's been sucking down too much home brew .
The knife .
Son of a bitch !
( Laughing )
( Johner ) Don 't push me , little Call . You hang with us for a while ,
you 'll find out I am not the man with whom to fuck !
It 's about time we start associating with a better class of people .
( Male Electronic voice Over Loudspeaker ) I am Father .
Welcome to the U.S.M. Auriga .
Step forward for contraband and weapons search .
Please report any infectious diseases ...
to the medical officers .
Levels 7 through 12 are off-limits to civilians . ( Device Whirring )
Thank you for your cooperation .
Go .
Get your hands up , please , sir . What ?
Could you get your hands up , please ?
( Device Whirring )
( Beeping )
There are no weapons allowed on board , sir .
My own recipe .
Way more dangerous .
Nice welcome , Perez . What the hell is this ?
What , are you afraid the six of us are gonna hijack your damn ship or what ?
Just a minor concern that one of your asshole crew members ...
is gonna get drunk and put a bullet through the hull .
We happen to be in space , Elgyn .
No shit . Howyou been ?
( Device Beeping )
Wanna check the chair ?
( Beeping Stops )
- Elgyn , these were very , very hard to come by . - ♪ ( Woman Singing Aria , Indistinct ) ♪
So was our cargo .
You 're , uh , not about to plead poverty on me , are you , General ?
No .
Just saying very few people deal in cash nowadays .
Just the ones don 't like to keep business records .
- Yourself , for example . - Drink , Elgyn ?
Constantly .
Now , I 'm gonna take a wild guess here , General ,
but I 'm thinking whatever you got going on here ,
it , uh , ain 't exactly approved by Congress .
Who 's the ...
new fillyyou got on board , Elgyn ?
Call . Little girl playing pirates .
She makes an impression . ( Chuckling )
She is severely fuckable , ain 't she ? ( Chuckles )
( Cackling )
Mighty handy with a monkey wrench too , I might add .
I think Vriess has got a bit of a light in his eye for her .
Fine little ass like that 'd make a man walk . You know what I mean ?
( Chuckling )
Mind you , uh , I think she 'sjust a tad curious ...
about , uh , this little transaction ofours .
I mean , I can 't say as I blame her .
It 's awfully cloak-and-dagger stuff .
It 's a military operation .
- Really ? - Mm-hmm .
Correct me if I 'm wrong , but , uh ,
I was under the impression that , uh ,
most army medical labs don 't have to operate outside of regulated space .
What do you want , Elgyn ? What can I do for you ?
Me ?
- Yeah . - Oh , two days bed and board .
You know , Vriess might wanna snag a part here or there , whatever .
I mean , uh , if it 's not imposing .
I don 't see any problem .
Couple ofconditions though . Ah .
Conditions ?
Not you ...
nor any of your ... ( Sniffs )
formidable crew members ...
will go anywhere near ...
restricted areas .
Rule number two :
No trouble .
Good behavior . Good behavior .
- No fights . - No fights .
Mi casa es su casa .
( Beeping )
( Beeping Continues )
( Father Over Loudspeaker ) Please direct cargo to med lab center , area " G. "
Follow the lit path .
Do not deviate .
Cargo status : Stable .
Life-forms intact .
Stasis uninterrupted .
Med lab center is off-limits to civilians .
Thank you .
( Alarm Beeping , Faint )
( Alarm Continues , Faint )
( Soft Screech )
( Screaming )
( ( Johner Chuckles )
Oh . Hey . Chill .
( Call ) Oh , please . You know I can 't lay off the tall ones .
Howyou doin ' ? How about a little one-on-one ?
What do you say ?
You got some moves on you , girl .
( Christie ) Oh , man .
Mm-hmm .
Well , now , if you don 't wanna play basketball , I know some other indoor sports .
( Sniffing )
Come on , now . Give me the ball .
( Groaning )
Okay , I got a new game .
Tag !
( Shouts )
Ripley ? Ripley .
( Whistles )
You 've had enough fun .
What the hell are you ?
( Chuckles )
Something of a predator , isn 't she ?
Yes , she continues to make us all very proud .
( Sighs )
( Moaning )
( Clicks )
( Wheelchair Motor Whirring )
( Woman ) We 're coming up on just one minute and 30 seconds left ...
to order this one-of-a-kind collector 's item .
Jesus Christ , Johner , what do you put in this shit , battery acid ?
Just for color .
( Clang )
( Growling Softly )
( Hisses )
( Snarls )
( Screeches )
( Buzzes )
( Hissing )
( Shrieking )
( Growls )
( Growling )
( Growling Stops )
So , we 're a fast learner .
( Woman ) Now here 's a fine item . This is a really good show , man .
( Woman ) It 's from the Gut Cutter 's Celebration Collection ,
makers of premier knives and edge ware .
The knife features a stainless steel blade ,
perfect for any use in hunting or in the home .
The pro handle is made from authentic antique plywood ...
and stained in brilliant colors for an uncanny charm .
Hey , man , that shit is not easy to come by !
Why don 't you take a walk outside ?
To a cutting edge that will rip through anything -
( Liquid Splashes ) Great !
I 'm so sorry . ( Christie ) Now I smell like this shit !
( Chuckling ) ( Johner ) Ifbitches can 't handle this shit ,
bitches should stay away from this shit !
( Christie ) Go to bed . Fucking bitch .
( Beeping )
( Father Over Loudspeaker ) Identification , please .
( Whirring , Buzzes ) Please try again .
- ( Chimes ) - Thank you , General Perez .
Well ?
You gonna kill me , orwhat ?
There 's no point , is there ?
They 've taken it out of you .
Where is it ? Is it on the ship ?
You mean my baby .
I don 't get it . If they took it out ,
why are they keeping you alive ?
Well , they 're curious . I 'm the latest thing .
Look .
I can make it all stop .
The pain , this nightmare . That 's all I can offeryou .
What makes you think ...
I would let you do that ?
Who are you ?
Ripley , Ellen , Lieutenant First Class ,
number 36706 .
Ellen Ripley died 200 years ago .
You 're not her .
I 'm not her .
( Sighs )
Who am I ?
You 're a thing , a construct . They grew you in a fucking lab .
And now they brought it out of you .
Not all the way out .
I can feel it ... behind my eyes .
I can hear it moving .
You gotta help me stop this thing before it gets loose .
It 's too late .
You can 't stop it .
It 's inevitable .
Not as long as I 'm around .
You 'll never get out of here alive .
I don 't care .
Really ?
( Whispers ) I can make it stop .
Go on . Get out of here .
They 're looking for you .
( Weapon Cocks , Whirring )
I think you 're gonna find that this was very ill-advised .
Where are her friends ? They 're in the mess hall , sir .
Well , you find them , now . Quietly .
What the hell is going on here ?
Smells like a double-cross , boss .
Where 's the other one ? With the chair ?
Don 't ever touch me .
Ever .
You wanna tell us what this is ?
You wanna tell me who you 're workin ' for . What ?
- Wren , they got nothing to do with this . - To do with what ?
Do you know what the penalties for terrorist activity are ?
No goddamn terrorists on my crew . Call , there something you wanna tell me ?
Look . I don 't care whether you knew or not . You brought a terrorist on board a military vessel .
And as far as I am concerned , you all die with her !
Do you understand ?
Yeah .
I understand .
Christie .
( Elgyn ) Down !
Freeze !
( Gunshot )
Stop ! Drop your weapons !
And you ! Drop that piece ofshit , or I blow his head off !
- Can 't do that , man . - Drop it now !
- Can 't do that . They 're attached to me . - I 'm not fucking with you !
You 're all under arrest for a code eight , which is concealed weapons ,
and a code 12 , which is murder !
Release Dr. Wren ! Kiss my ass .
Put down yourweapons and assume the fucking -
( Groans , Coughs )
Everybody okay ?
( Soldier Coughs Over Monitor ) ( Johner Over Monitor ) Real easy , soldier boy .
( Man ) Security . Get up !
There is a serious problem in the mess hall .
You lie to me now , little girl ,
I will cut your throat and leave you here to die , you understand me ?
( Man ) This is security , Section 2 . We do not read you . Hello ? Goddamn it ! Hello ?
We do not copyyou . Please repeat .
Hello ? Please repeat .
( Growling )
( Snarling )
( Both Hissing )
( Shrieking )
( Shrieking , Snarling Continue )
( Shrieks )
( Shrieking )
( Screeches )
( Sizzling )
( Whimpering )
Gediman !
He 's conducting illegal experiments . He is breeding some sort of -
( Johner ) Ice the goddamn mole ! Listen to me ! He is breeding an alien species .
More than dangerous . Ifthose things get loose ,
it 's gonna make the Lacerta plague look like a fucking square dance !
Shut up ! ( Alarm Blaring , Faint )
Listen .
( Alarm Blaring ) ( Father Over Loudspeaker ) Your attention , please .
Security breach , med lab , Level 15 .
( Breathing Heavily )
( Screaming )
( Roaring )
( Gunshot ) ( Man Screaming )
( Machine Gun Fire ) ( Men Shouting )
Go . Let 's get back to the Betty . Doctor and soldier boy here can see us to the door .
( Woman ) What about Vriess ? ( Johner ) Fuck Vriess .
( Father ) Your attention , please .
Unauthorized opening ofcage three .
Unauthorized opening ofcages five ,
seven , eight , 10
( Move it ! Now ! - ( Father ) Evacuation .
- Go ! Go now ! - Evacuation .
( Shrieking )
( Snarling )
( Father ) This is not a drill .
- Evacuation . - Move it ! Go ! Get on board !
Your attention , please .
Nonhuman presence detected ,
Levels 21 , 23 ,
27 , 14 ,
Level 38 , Level 39 .
- ( Hissing ) - Evacuation .
Proceed to lifeboats .
This is not a drill .
Thank you for your cooperation .
( Growls )
( Roars )
( Grunting )
( Snarling )
( Groaning )
( Screaming )
( Roaring ) - I 'll give you holes , you slimy bastard !
( Shouting )
Move it ! Let 's go !
- ( Father ) Final lifeboat ready for launch . - Get aboard !
( Growling )
( All Shouting ) Go !
( Father ) Complete evacuation now .
( All Screaming )
( Screaming )
Grenade .
- ( Growling ) - ( Gasping )
( Growling )
( Father ) Alert . Alert .
Evacuation incomplete .
Civilian presence detected in area " H. " Warning .
Main vessel declared uninhabitable .
( Alarm Blaring , Faint )
( Christie ) Elgyn , come on . Let 's move , man .
Yeah .
( Hissing )
( Woman ) Elgyn ? Elgyn , where are you ?
Elgyn , where are you ?
( Christie ) Elgyn ?
( Clatter )
( Snarls )
( Groaning )
( Woman ) Elgyn !
God . Elgyn ? ( Christie ) Elgyn ?
Elgyn !
( ( Johner ) Easy , Hillard ! Christie , give me a hand here !
Get him up ! Give me a hand here !
( Hillard ) Come on ! Let 's get him up ! Move out of the way !
( Sobbing ) No ! Ah , shit .
What the fuck did this ? What 's in this place ?
( Roaring )
- ( ( Johner ) Call , get down ! - ( Christie ) What the fuck is that ?
Don 't shoot ! It 's in front of the hull !
( Snarling )
What is that ?
Come on , man . Time to go . Time to go ! ( Christie ) Get back !
- ( Roaring ) - Damn !
Call , time to go ! Come on , Call !
Get the goddamn door open ! ( All Shouting )
We can 't open it ! We can 't open the door !
( Shouting Continues )
( Soldier ) We gotta go back ! - ( Johner ) I 'm not going back ! You go back !
( Hisses )
- What the fuck ? - ( Ripley Panting )
Was it everything you hoped for ?
( Hillard ) Leave him alone !
What do we do now , man ?
Same thing we 're doin ' . Get the hell outta here ! What if there 's more ?
I say we stay here , man . Let the army guys deal .
Where the fuck are the army guys ?
They 're dead !
Well , then we don 't need this asshole anymore .
- Step back ! - No , you step back !
- Stop it ! - You got no authority here !
( Alarm Blaring , Faint )
Doctor , that thing that killed my partner ,
that 's your pet science project ? Yes .
- Let me do him right now , man ! - I should let him do you right now !
How many more are there ?
How many more are there ? Twelve .
- ( Johner ) Twelve ? - Twelve .
Twelve .
There 'll be more .
So ,
who do I have to fuck to get off this boat ?
I can get you off . Maybe not the boat , but -
Let 's get out of here . No , wait a second here .
She was the host for these monsters .
Wren cloned her because she had one inside her .
She 's not human .
She was part of his experiment , and she will turn on us in a second .
( Christie ) I don 't give a shit what she is .
( Call ) She 's too much of a risk . We have to leave her .
- She comes . - We can 't trust her !
I don 't trust anyone .
Ifwe 're gonna survive this mess , we all stick together .
Agreed ?
Hillard , we gotta go . It 's not over . We gotta get to the Betty .
( Grunts )
Make a nice souvenir .
I can 't believe you did that .
Did what ? Killed one of 'em .
It 's like killing your own kind . It was in my way .
( Beeps )
( Christie Exhales ) Oh , man !
Who were you expecting , Santa Claus ?
( Sighs ) - Thought you were toast for certain , man .
Shit . Where 's Elgyn ?
Oh , shit .
Hey , man , what if we get to the Betty and they 're all over it ?
All the activity 's been in the aft sector by the barracks . Why would they move ?
( Ripley ) They won 't .
If they send anyone out ,
it 'll be , uh , here ,
where the meat is .
Yeah . Well , I say if we wanna make any decent time , I say we ditch the cripple .
- No offense , man . - None taken .
Nobody is left behind . Not even you , Johner .
- What 's the quickest way out of here ? - After the cooling tower ,
there 's a freight elevator .
It runs from the top of the ship down to Engineering Level 1 deck .
- Take us straight to the dock . - Sounds reasonable . Let 's do it .
We 're moving .
What ? - ( Ripley ) The ship is moving .
I can feel it .
The ship has stealth run . There 's no wayyou can tell .
She 's right .
The ship 's been go since the attack .
That 's a standard emergency procedure . That 's right .
Any serious problem , and the ship autopilots back to home base .
And you were planning on letting us know this ?
Nobody asked .
- ( Scoffs ) - What 's home base ?
Earth .
Oh , great .
- Bastard . - ( Johner ) Earth ?
I 'd rather stay here with the things , man .
How long until we get to Earth ?
Three hours almost .
We gotta blow the ship .
Call , you 're not blowing this ship .
Not while we 're on it , okay ?
We get out of this shit , you do as you please , all right ?
Earth , man . What a shit-hole .
( Ripley ) It 's clear .
Hey , Ripley .
I heard you , like , ran into these things before .
That 's right . Wow , man .
So , like , what did you do ?
I died .
( Wheelchair Whirring )
( Soldier ) Not that way !
( Christie ) Ripley .
( Christie ) Ripley , come on .
Ripley , we got no time for sightseeing here .
( Wren ) Ripley , don 't .
( Gasping )
( Sobs )
( Grunts )
( Machine Beeping )
( Groaning )
( Gasps )
Hel -
Kill ... me .
Kill me .
( Beeping Continues )
( Grunts )
( Breathing Heavily )
Don 't do it , Ripley .
Don 't do what ?
What 's the big deal , man ?
Fuckin ' waste ofammo .
Let 's go .
Must be a chick thing .
( Breathing Heavily )
( Faint Snarl )
( Hisses )
Am I dreaming , or is this not the shit we brought with us ?
Yeah , it 's the same shit .
Stinks in here , man . Let 's keep moving .
( Screams )
Get away from me ! Get away from me !
Drop the rod , man . Get away from me !
- Do it ! - Get away from me .
( Clangs ) Get away from me .
Who are you people ?
What 's happening here ? ( Christie ) Calm down .
What 's happening here is we 're getting the fuck off this ghost ship , okay ?
Ship ? What ship ?
Where am I ?
I was in cryo , right ? On my way to Xarem , right ?
Work crew for the nickel refinery , right ?
I wake up . I know I don 't understand .
Oh , God . Uh , I s-I saw - I saw horrible things .
Look , you 're coming with us . It 's too dangerous for you here .
( Breathing Erratically )
( Sniffing )
Leave him .
Fuck you . We 're not leaving him here .
He 's got one inside of him .
I can smell it .
( Man ) Inside me ?
Inside me ? What 's inside me ? ( Johner ) Hey , man .
I don 't want one of those things birthing anywhere near my ass .
It 's a bad risk .
- What 's inside me ? - Look , we can 't just leave him here .
I thought you came here to stop ' em from spreadin ' .
What 's inside me ?
There 's gotta be a process . Can 't you stop it ?
( Christie ) Got no time for that .
I can 't do it here . The lab is out oforder .
What 's inside me ?
I could do him . Back of the head .
Painless . It might be the best way .
- What 's inside me ? - No , there 's got to be another way .
( Call ) What if we freeze him ? What 's in-fuckin ' - side me ?
A parasite !
Foreign element .
There 's a monster in your chest .
These guys hijacked your ship ,
and they sold your cryo tube ...
to this ... human ,
and he put an alien inside of you .
It 's a really nasty one .
And in a few hours , it 's gonna burst its way through your rib cage ...
and you 're gonna die .
Any questions ?
( Breathing Erratically )
Who are you ?
I 'm the monster 's mother .
( Call ) Look , he comes with us , we freeze him on the Betty ,
- then the doctor can remove it later . - Fine with me .
Since when were you in goddamn charge ?
- Since you were born without balls ! - Ease off , people .
All right . You come with us . You might even live .
( Christie ) Get twitchy on me , and you 'll be shot .
Let 's move out .
( ( Johner ) It 's a mess down there ! Is this the only way ?
Vriess , we gotta lose the chair .
I know .
Kawlang maneuver , all right ?
Yeah , just like old times . Yeah .
Must be the cooling tanks .
Somebody must have opened the valves .
The nasties couldn 't have done this , could they ?
We 're at the bottom of the ship .
We have to go through the kitchen , maybe 90 feet ,
to the freight elevator on the other side .
- I don 't like it . - What 's to like ?
This sucks !
- Wren , are you sure about the distance ? - Yes .
- You ready to get wet , partner ? - Yeah .
( Coughs )
Hey , uh , do your weapons fire underwater ?
Yeah , they 're disposables . They can take it .
Disposables ?
( Laughing ) Hey , I heard about those . Yeah .
- How many rounds ? - Twenty .
Split points give you a good hole , even at the smaller caliber .
Oh . Hey , that 's cool . ( Laughing )
Yeah . They 're big with hitters ' cause you , uh , throw ' em away after the job .
Nobody likes to throw away a weapon they 're attached to . You know what I mean ?
Yeah .
Guess I don 't have to tell everyone to take a deep breath .
( Chuckles )
( Vriess ) Hey , Christie , do me a favor .
When we hit the surface on the other side ,
no backstroke , okay ?
( Shouts )
( Screaming )
( Growling )
( Screams )
( Moaning )
( Grunts )
( Screams )
( All Gasping )
- ( Gasps ) - Jesus Christ !
( Gasps )
They set a goddamn trap .
It 's a goddamn ambush !
( Screeches )
( No Audible Dialogue )
( Roaring )
Distephano !
( Snarls )
It won 't break . Give me yourweapon .
You really are way too trusting .
No !
You killed her ! You bastard !
- I 'll get you ! - ( Chamber Clicks )
Father , lock the door .
- Christie ! Climb ! Climb ! - ( Snarls )
I 'm doin ' it , man ! Come on !
Come on ! ( Snarls )
It 'sjammed ! Move it !
It 'sjammed ! ( Grunts )
( Shots Firing )
( Vriess Muttering )
( Screams )
( Screaming )
( Grunting )
( Snarls )
( Roaring )
( Screams )
Get off my foot , bitch !
( Groaning )
( Snarling ) ( Christie ) Get off me !
( Grunts ) Johner !
Get off me ! Get off me !
Aaah ! Johner !
Die , motherfucker !
- Do it , man ! - ( Snarls )
- Hey ! - ( Snarls )
( Screeches )
( Gasps )
Real nice party , ain 't it ?
( Groaning )
( Grunts )
( Groaning , Sobbing )
Christie ! Christie !
Christie ! No !
Christie !
What are you doing ? Don 't do it !
Don 't ! We can make it !
- No ! - ( Screams )
- ( Groaning , Sobbing ) - Damn !
( Grunting )
( Breathing Erratically )
( Alarm Beeping )
( Grunts )
This way .
Come on !
Baby , am I glad to see you .
I was sure that asshole got you . Are you hurt ?
I 'm fine .
You got body armor on ? Yeah . Come on .
You took it in the chest . I saw it .
( Chuckles )
You 're a robot ?
Son of a bitch ! Our little Call is just full ofsurprises .
I should have known . No human being is that humane .
I thought synthetics were supposed to be all logical and shit .
You 'rejust a big old psycho , girl .
- You 're a robot ? - You 're a second gen , aren 't you ?
You 're an Auton .
Robots designed by robots , right ? Hah !
Oh , yeah . That 's right . I remember .
Now , they were supposed to revitalize the synthetic industry .
Instead , they buried it .
( Chuckles ) They didn 't like being told what to do .
Government ordered a recall .
Now , I heard - I had-I had heard ...
that only a few-just a few-had gotten out intact .
Man , I never , never thought that I would see one !
Great . She 's a toaster oven .
Can we leave now ?
( Distephano Laughing ) - ( Ripley ) How long before we land ?
( Distephano ) Just under two hours . ( Johner ) Hey , Vriess .
You got a socket wrench ? Maybe shejust needs an oil change .
( Father ) I 'm sorry . Access denied . I can 't believe I almost fucked it .
Yeah , like you never fucked a robot !
( Ripley ) You know , ifWren gets in the computer , he could really screw us .
( Johner ) We gotta find a terminal . No , there 's no console on this level .
We 'd have to go back . Well , we can 't go back .
And I don 't know any of Wren 's access codes .
Help me .
Call .
No . I can 't .
Right . You 're the new model droid .
You can access the mainframe by remote . No , I can 't .
I burned my modem . We all did .
Call , you can still patch in manually . You know that .
( Distephano ) There 's ports in the chapel , up there .
Call .
You 're programmed for that ? Don 't make me do this .
Don 't make me make you .
( Sighs ) I don 't want to go in there .
It 's like my insides are liquid . It 's not real .
Get over it .
You can blow the ship before it reaches Earth ...
and kill them all .
( Sniffles )
Just give us time to get out first .
Damn it . Anything ?
Hold on .
( ComputerVoice ) Breach in Sector 7 , Sector 3 .
Sector 9 unstable .
Engines operating at 41 % .
Eighty-six minutes until Earth dock . ( Sighs )
( Normal Voice ) We burned too much energy .
I can 't make critical mass . I can 't blow it .
Then crash it .
( Grunting ) ( Grunting ) Yeah .
( Gasping )
( Grunting )
I 'm okay . I 'm okay .
Really .
I feel good .
( Call : Computer Voice ) Ground level recalibrated .
New destination : 7-6-0-4-0-3 .
Uninhabited quadrant .
Braking systems off-lined . Acceleration increase .
Time until impact now 43 minutes , 8 seconds .
Try to clear us a path to the Betty ...
and start her up .
( Normal Voice ) Okay .
( Whirring , Beeping )
( ComputerVoice ) Please wait .
Emergency override in console 45V , Level 1 .
( Gasps )
( Normal Voice ) It 's Wren . He 's almost at the Betty .
( Beeping )
- ( Buzzes ) - ( Powering Down )
Father , locate the power drain . Report .
Father ? Father !
( Call Over Speaker ) Father 's dead , asshole .
Intruder on Level 1 .
All aliens , please proceed to Level 1 .
You got a mean streak .
( Groans ) Damn it . Let me see .
- Don 't touch me . - Come on .
You must think this is pretty funny .
I 'm finding a lot of things funny lately ,
but I don 't think they are .
Why do you go on living ?
How can you stand being what you are ?
Not much choice .
At least there 's a part of you that 's human .
( Sighs ) I 'm just-Look at me .
I 'm disgusting .
Why did you come here ?
To kill you , remember ?
Before the recall ,
I accessed the mainframe .
Every dirty little covert op the government ever dreamed of is in there .
And this-you , the aliens ,
even the crew from the Betty-I knew ifthey succeeded , it would be the end of them .
Why do you care what happens to them ?
Because I 'm programmed to .
You 're programmed to be an asshole ?
You 're the new asshole model they 're putting out ?
Come on .
I couldn 't watch ' em do it .
I couldn 't let ' em annihilate themselves .
Do you understand that ?
I did once .
I tried to save ... people .
It didn 't work out .
There was this girl .
She had bad dreams .
I tried to help her .
She died .
Now I can 't even remember her name .
I guess we 're almost there .
( Ripley ) Right .
( Ripley Sighs ) Do you dream ?
( Call ) I-Well , we have neuroprocessors that-Yes .
( Ripley ) When I sleep , I dream about them-it .
Every night . All around me , in me .
I used to be afraid to dream , but I 'm not anymore .
Why ? ( Ripley Chuckles )
Because no matter how bad the dreams get ,
when I wake up , it 's always worse .
- ( Distephano ) It 's not so far now ! - God , I 'm so tired .
( ( Johner ) Sleep when you die , man .
Oh , no . This is bad , right ?
- I think we 're near the nest . - Well , then we 'll go another way .
We don 't have time . We got nearly 90 minutes .
- Not anymore . - What are you saying ?
- What did you do , robot ? - Let 's go . Come on .
Hey ! You want to die here with your little brothers and sisters , that 's cool !
But I plan to live past today !
Ifthis little hunk of plastic is pulling any shit ,
I 'm gonna kill her !
Kill you ! Does that compute ?
Or do I have to drawyou a schematic ?
( Gagging ) Hey !
- You want another souvenir ? - ( Gagging Continues )
- How far are the docks ? - A h-hundred yards .
Ripley .
Come on .
Ripley , we have to go .
I hear them .
I hear them . They 're so close .
Ripley . It 's the queen .
She 's in pain .
- ( Screams ) - Ripley !
Ripley !
Wait !
Oh , my God .
( Man ) We gotta be moving .
The best thing you can do is pray for a quick death .
Come on . Come on .
It 's not right .
( Man ) I 've been saying that all day .
( Vriess ) It 's up to you now , Call .
I need you to patch into the ship again and open the hatch .
( Computer Beeping )
( Beeps )
Johner , we should put Purvis in the freezer now .
( ( Johner ) All right , little buddy .
Nap time .
( Screams )
- Oh ! - ( Call Whimpering )
Nobody moves , or I put a cap ...
right where this little droid 's brain is .
Distephano , take the weapons .
Begging your pardon , sir , but fuckyou !
Oh , fine . Then I kill her , and you kill me ,
and we all die , and nobody goes home !
Now drop the weapon .
Then this little synthetic bitch ...
is gonna plug into the Auriga ,
and she is gonna take us right back to home base ,
according to the standard emergency procedures .
- No , she 's not . - ( Distephano ) Are you crazy ?
You still want to bring those things back to Earth ?
Haven 't you been paying any attention today ?
Ah , the intellectual speaks .
Stay there ! Listen , if you don 't -
Don 't you ever shut up ?
( Groaning )
( Grunting )
- Why does nobody listen to me ? - ( Grunting )
( Screaming )
( Screeching )
( Screeching Continues )
( Shouting )
( Gediman ) I told you . At first , everything was normal .
The queen laid her eggs . But then she started to change .
She added a second cycle cell .
So ,
this time there is no host .
There are no eggs .
There is only herwomb ...
and the creature inside .
That is Ripley 's gift to her :
A human reproductive system .
She is giving birth for you , Ripley ,
and now she is perfect !
( Growling )
( Roaring )
( Groans )
( Screeching )
( Gasping )
( Screeching Continues )
( Roars )
( Roaring )
You are ...
a beautiful ,
beautiful butterfly .
( Roars )
( Growls )
( High-pitched Whine )
- No . - ( Roars )
( Screeching )
No . No .
( Roaring )
( Growling )
( High-pitched Whine )
( Growls )
( Sniffing )
( Gasps )
( Low Growl )
Ah , look . Look .
Beautiful , beautiful little baby .
Look . It thinks you 're its mother .
Come on .
( Chittering ) Come on .
( High-pitched Whine )
Yeah .
Come on . ( Growls )
( Screaming )
( Groans )
( Roaring )
( Father ) Civilian vessel on line .
Emergency departure authorized .
( Panting )
All right . She 's hot . I 'll open the Auriga 's air locks , pull the holding clamps on your mark .
Right . I-I just need to find , uh , the , uh -
th-the vertical thrust lock .
Are you sure you guys can fly this thing ? Yes !
- ( Father ) Launch status is go . - No !
Ripley .
( Beeps )
( Shouting )
- Hey . - I thought you were dead .
Yeah , I get that a lot . Why are we still here ?
Uh , I 'm just , uh , finding the , uh , manual override .
- For Christ 's sake . - ( Johner ) Hey , Ripley .
Good memory . Excuse me .
Ripley 's back , man . Is that it ?
Nope .
You can 't fly one of these things too , can you ?
Are you kidding ? This piece ofshit is even older than I am .
( Beeping ) - Goddamn it . We 've still got breach . The hatch .
I closed it .
Fixed the goddamn hatch a hundred times , man !
- I 'll get it . I 'll get it . - ( Exhales )
( Beeps )
( Electricity Buzzes )
( Father ) Approaching Earth 's atmosphere .
Window ofdeparture now 46 seconds .
Call , we have to go .
- ( Beeping ) - Call .
We 've gotta get out of here .
- ( Roars ) - ( Gasps )
( Father ) Window ofdeparture now 20 seconds .
( Beeps )
Grab on to something , Call . We 're outta here .
( Roars )
( Grunting )
( Roaring )
Come on , baby .
- ( Groans ) - This thing is gonna fall apart .
Pressure 's unstable !
Go help Call turn on the auxiliary pump !
- ( Roaring ) - ( Whimpers )
( High-pitched Whine )
( Roars )
( Whimpers )
( Growls )
( Murmurs )
Distephano ?
( Growls )
( Roars )
- ( Gasping ) - ( Screeches )
Come on ! Step on it !
Hey , I 'm not the mechanic here , Ironsides !
I mostlyjust hurt people !
Shit . Call !
Call , get back up here !
Call ! Call !
Ripley ! Hey , Ripley !
Johner , where are you , you son of a bitch ?
- Get on it , bastard ! - What am I supposed to do ?
Grab the sticks .
( Low Groaning )
( Roars )
Put her down .
( Low Murmuring )
Oh .
( Low Groaning )
( Murmuring )
( Murmuring Continues )
( Sighs )
( Electricity Crackles )
( Sizzling )
( Screeches )
( Roars )
( Screaming , Roaring )
Ripley !
( Screaming , Roaring Continue )
( Groans )
( Screaming ) Oh , no !
Oh , no !
I 'm sorry .
( Screaming , Shouting ) No !
( Screaming )
( Both Gasping )
( Father ) U.S.M. Auriga will impact in five seconds .
Four . Three .
Two . One .
Thank you .
( Whooshing )
- ( Johner Screaming ) - ( Computer Beeping )
( Whimpers )
- What 's burnin ' ? - Us !
Shit ! You 're right ! ( Screaming ) - ( Screaming )
( Both Sigh )
( Call ) So this is Earth , huh ?
( Ripley ) This is Earth .
This is my first time here .
I suppose the military will be sniffing around here pretty soon . ( Sniffs )
Bet you 're not too anxious to see them .
Not really .
You know , a person could get pretty lost around here ifthey wanted to .
What do you think ?
What should we do ?
I don 't know .
I 'm a stranger here myself .